BGM
Here we go, Apkami!
This time we have with us Sakura Ishiyama from Juice Juice
and Akari Endo from Juice Juice.
This show is about the behind-the-scenes production of various artists
This show is about the behind-the-scenes production of the various artists who belong to the Upfront Group.
our recording sessions and rehearsals.
We will show you the process of our recording and rehearsal.
Let's start with the behind-the-scenes of the two MCs.
I, Ishiyama, would like to talk about the concert of Hello Project as a whole.
I've experienced "2 of us" and "3 of us" before, but I've never experienced a concert of the whole Hello Project group.
I have experienced 2 of us and 3 of us, but this is the first time for me to attend a concert of the whole Hello Project group.
I'm very excited to be able to rehearse together with the other members of the Hello Project.
It was a very stimulating concert for me because I was able to rehearse together with them, and I hope to grow and develop through this concert.
I hope to grow and develop through this concert.
This will be the first time for me to perform with the whole group.
I have a lot to learn every day, and I hope to do my best from now on.
And I, Endo, have many chances to perform at various summer festivals.
I'd like to talk about him.
When I perform at various summer festivals
I'm sure there are many other fans there.
I think that JuiceJuice's fans are very united.
I think that JuiceJuice fans are very united.
I'm always happy to see them at festivals, and I'm always happy to hear them raise their voices to us.
I'm very happy to see them at festivals.
I'd like to do my best to give a performance that can respond to them.
I hope we can make this summer as fun as the stage and the audience's enthusiasm.
Now, let's start with this après-campaign.
Morning Musume。24ななんかセンチimentalな時の歌 Music Video Filming Making
Here's a look at the making of the music video for Morning Musume。 24's latest single, "Somewhat Sentimental Song", which was released on August 14!
The making of music video shootingThe shooting of the music video for the song "Sentimental Moments" from the latest single of Morning Musume。
Filming for the music video has begun!
I'm a grown-up and a Barbie-in-Better.
It's the first time we're filming outside in the dark.
I'm a little bit excited.
It's early in the morning, but I'll do my best.
The night is deep, too. On the contrary, it's heavy.
After spending Y's and Y's, my heart is falling
Just friends, friends of Saleh
Two or three at a time, it's just exhaustion
I'm sure it was a long time ago
I'm so excited!
You weren't always like this
I could be like that with anyone.
I used to have a good time
Today, we're shooting a music video for a song about sentimental times.
I'm shooting a music video for a sentimental song.
It's pretty dark inside.
But I thought the lyrics sounded like it was going to clear up.
We shot it outside like this.
So we didn't get too caught up in the weight of the lyrics.
I didn't get too caught up in the weight of the lyrics.
I'll do my best until the end.
Next Episode
Next time preview
Each person's solo part was quite long.
There were a lot of scenes where we didn't sing.
I tried my best to change my hands and facial expressions.
Also, this time
I couldn't imagine so many sentimental music videos.
I didn't expect it to be shot outdoors.
That was also very interesting and unexpected.
I'm looking forward to seeing the finished product.
The two of you walk in a straight line.
The best part is when they come together.
Okay, I'll go.
Okay, I'm going.
Good luck!
Laser start!
Let's go.
Cut.
Music.
Immediately Filmed
Thank you for watching
But still friends
Two or three times is just exhaustion
I'm sure that once upon a time
I'm sure she wasn't like this
You're not like anyone else.
No, I wasn't.
I had a great time.
It's just that this time it's sod.
Yes, it was.
It feels like it's been a while.
Yes, as Morning Musume。 As for Morning Musume.
The wind felt really good.
And the scene where you're stretching a little bit
I hope it will be used.
It's a little bit like this.
It's a song that really needs to have a world view
I don't know...
It's open.
The chorus...
You want to dance, don't you?
The A melody is all "shun, shun, shun".
But the chorus, the way everyone is moving forward...
I feel like I was able to dance with a good sense of openness.
I hope you can feel that.
It feels good.
The more you put me on top of you, the more difficult it feels.
All the tears are transparent
Not a single cloud, not a single pure imite
Everything inside me is clear
As I was when I was a child
As it was when I was a little girl
Yes
I'm not looking for luxury
I just want to be simple
I'm just looking at all these videos and I'm just looking at them.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you for all your hard work.
I had a good time with people
Thank you for your hard work
We've finished shooting the music video.
I don't know how the song is going to be sung... and I don't know how the song will be sung... and I don't know how the music video is going to look like...
We didn't know how the song was going to be sung, how the costumes were going to be, and how the music video was going to look like.
I was so surprised to see them wearing all white and shooting outdoors like this.
It's been a long time since you've taken pictures, right? It was the first time to shoot outdoors.
I think we used to shoot outdoors with green backdrops, and the strongest of us used to shoot outdoors with green backdrops,
We shot outside, and we shot in groups using various locations,
I have only shot one group, so I am looking forward to seeing how the other groups do it,
I'm looking forward to seeing the finished product soon.
I can't wait to see the finished product, and I hope you will all watch it as much as possible when it is completed.
I can't wait to see it.
I was able to observe the first performance of this song at Nippon Budokan, and I had the strong impression that the atmosphere of the concert itself changed completely the moment the song started and the music started,
I personally think that the atmosphere of the song reminded me of black and gray,
I personally think that the atmosphere of the song reminds me of black and gray, but the costumes are all white and there is a gap between the two.
Yes, I think Morning Musume's costumes are flashy and beautiful and cool.
I have an image that Morning Musume usually wear flashy, beautiful and cool costumes.
But this all-white costume is so simple and simple without any decoration.
I thought it would be better to shoot outdoors in a simple place without any decorations, and the dance was done as it was.
And the way they filmed the dance.
It was really cool to see a different side of Morning Musume.
This was the making of the music video for Morning Musume 24's somewhat sentimental song.
Morning Musume。24
Somewhat Sentimental Song
Now on sale
Don't forget to stay hydrated!
Here is the next one!
Juice Juice Naemono Love Vocal Recording
From Juice Juice's latest single
Miaomono Love Dambaralulu Vocal Recording
Here you go! Now, is there anything you don't understand?
No!
Yes!
Let's go all the way up to "2Block is so cute" in the A melody...
Shy boy, you know who you are...
But you're a little short on excitement.
I'm a little nervous about the surprise present you're going to give me.
You don't even notice the new nails or the new hairdo.
He compliments you on your hair, strokes you, tells you how pretty you are.
Okay, um, sorry.
I think I'll just give it to you.
Okay.
Well, you know, it doesn't hurt that you're singing right now.
For someone who just said you rock...
It's like that.
A strong girl is totally fine.
Yes.
Um...
I was thinking of wearing a river girl dress.
Okay.
Please sing.
Okay, I'll open it.
Canebar.
Shy boy, you know who you are
I know I'm a shy boy But I'm not exciting enough
Give me that.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on.
I'm so excited, I'm so excited, I'm so excited, I'm so excited, I'm so excited, I'm so excited.
That's good.
Yes, yes, we'll do more preparation from there.
Yes, okay.
Okay, okay.
Okay, let's go to B melody.
Love with a dangerous scent might be nice
To someone exciting.
What should I usually do?
Let's go to the different-colored Nori no Kata.
Let's go up to the chorus, "I'm longing for you.
I'll go to the one with
me I'm so eye-rolling.
I want life, Lee. I want life, Lee. I want life, Lee. I want life, Lee. I want life, Lee.
The truth is, I'm really
I'm longing for you
The first two lines are absolutely fine as they are now.
I felt like I was singing with a little bit of exploration in this area as well,
I'm totally OK with the way it is now, so you can gut it out like that.
Yes, let's go!
Enjoy the next time!
I'm about to be impressed by an irritating person.
Life is a prayer Matching pacas
I actually admire you very much.
The second half, life is a prayer, matching paca
Let's just try this one.
To someone exciting, I'm going to ruin it.
Life is a prayer... and matching pacas.
I really, really, really admire you.
Yes, sir.
Let's go rusty.
Let's go rust.
Let's go to Sabi.
To put it in great detail,
The pitch when she sang "I'll seek your love, love, love.
I don't have it, I don't have it, I don't have it.
Subtle.
You know?
Wait a minute.
Just a little bit.
Love, love, love.
Yes, yes, yes.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Well...
Isn't it this way?
And the "E" part of the "no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm going to say, "I've got nothing, nothing, nothing, nothing.
I don't know what it's called, but if you go with the rhythm, that's where it goes, but the timing of the "E" in the "na-na-na-na-na" I just mentioned, it's better to go back a little bit.
Like "nai nai nai nai nai nai nai nai nai nai nai nai nai nai nai".
I always say, "It's not a thing, it's a thing, it's always a thing.
So a little bit back, like a little bit back, like a little bit back, like a little bit back.
A little bit back.
Yes.
That kind of image.
Yes, yes.
That's a good one. - Yeah.
I really admire you.
Yes, I do.
I'm always begging for something I don't have.
That's why even a vague line isn't enough.
I know I can't measure up, I know I can't measure up, it's not easy
I yearn for your love, love, love, love, my darling.
That's all.
Thank you very much.
I knew it! I knew it! I knew it!
From the name of the song, you might think it's a cute song.
I'm sure you're thinking of a cute song.
but as you can see in the recording of Dambara-san's song
but as you can see from the recording of Dambara's song
you can see that it's a rock song
You can see the cool side of Dambara in this song.
including the cool and funny parts of the music video.
I hope you enjoy the gap between the cool and the funny parts of the music video.
I hope you can enjoy the gap between the cool and the funny parts of the music video.
I listened to the song when I received the tentative soundtrack
I tried to listen to this song when I received the tentative soundtrack of this song.
I remember that I felt it was a new song for Juice Juice.
By the time I was ready to record this song, I had a feeling that it was a new song for Juice Juice.
I was not able to imagine what it would be like if Juice Juice sang this song.
I couldn't really imagine what it would be like if Juice Juice sang this song, but let's hear Dambara's recording.
But after listening to Dambara-san's recording of the song, I was able to get an idea of what it would be like if she sang it.
I felt that any song becomes Juice Juice when Dambara-san sings it.
That's all.
This is Juice Juice Juice's vocal recording of "Naemono Love Dambaralulu".
I'm always on your side
Sakura Ishiyama from Juice Juice Juice and Akari Endo from Juice Juice are presenting Red Hair, and here they are!
Angulum Vivitar Ichigeki Vocal Recording
Here's a look at the vocal recording of Waka Matsumoto from Angulum's latest single, "Vivitar Ichigeki"!
Okay, let's start with the A melody.
Skeuzak-sama ga nee nee nee nee nee, up to my worth
Yes, sir.
Let's do it!
Please do
BGM
I'm a picture of hurt, not a single tear, not a shelf, not a king
A strike of the imagination, a strike of the imagination, I won't let you take it away from me, my value
I've already got the melody and the lyrics and everything.
Well... well... if I may say so...
I dare say...
It's fine the way you're doing it now, but let's try to make it a little stronger and more lively.
Let's try it again.
Kizutsukusowa becomes a picture, not a single tear.
Not a single tear, not a single blip, not an ounce, not a single storm strike, not an ounce of imagination.
I won't let you take away my value
OK, I'll go to B's place now!
B's third string should be trained one day, the glorious day before.
You don't have to sing this one right now.
I'm going to go now.
I'm going to go to the end.
I'll talk you out of it, I can't even imagine.
I won't let you take away my value
My rule is not to show you after all my efforts
But I'll use it as a shield and push forward
Don't worry, I'll be fine.
I'll see you later. I have to go.
Excuse me.
Okay, okay. That's fine.
Yeah, but...
But if it's easier to play by the rules, that's fine.
Really?
Yeah. Go ahead and make fun of me.
Yes, I understand.
I'll see you later. I'm leaving.
Ignore the loneliness. Please go ahead.
You can't take away my value.
My rule is not to show you after all my efforts. But I'll use it as a shield and push forward.
I'll see you later. I have to go.
Yes!
Now the days when my chest swells up are my bible
I embrace even the pain and sarcasm
Let's go!
I'll see you later
Now the days when my chest swells up are my bible
I embrace even pain and sarcasm
Oh, my God! You're a Pasan!
I don't care anymore,
I embrace even pain and sarcasm
This Tintin Tintin
Let's put a little more emphasis on it.
I'll see you later, I've got to go.
Now my chest swells, every day is a bible
I'll embrace even pain and sarcasm
I'll rust.
Let's do it once.
Thank you for watching.
When it's carved, the tires will shine One after the other they'll push in
Survive the belief Survive the belief I'm not gonna lose yet at a place like this
I'm going to get what I want Don't be scared
I'm gonna love you.
Oh, there's nothing more to say.
It's perfect.
You're not having a hard time, are you?
I'm fine.
Well then, I'm not sure if it's just one song, so please sing one more.
Here we go.
Rattle-peep.
Ending
When it's carved, the tires glow
One after the other, one after the other
Survive the trials and tribulations
I'm not gonna let this place beat me yet
I'm the one who's gonna get what I want
Don't be scared, don't be scared
I'm gonna love you
I'll love you.
Okay, let's rap between number one and number two.
Let's do it.
Perfect!
The blade eye is perfect!
I was stimulating.
Stimulus is hard, isn't it?
I have no idea what to say here.
I need stimulation.
I want stimulation.
This is the hardest part. I think it probably differs from person to person, but there are many people who get stuck on this stimulus.
I think that stimulus and I'd like to savor are difficult.
I've got the right frame of mind, so now it's just a matter of how well I can say the words.
Yes, I will do my best.
I'll do my best. I'm not so sure if I can say the words, or if I can say them with feeling.
Okay, let's try.
Yes, let's go for it.
It's not worth it if it's all sweet. Tell me, what flavor do you really want?
I'd like to savor
The chosen heroine, the chosen storm
Three, two, one, I'll never give up hope in myself until I can ride it out
I feel like I'm not giving up.
Okay, that's it.
That's all for now.
Thank you very much.
Your voice is very straight and it is very easy to listen to, and there is a fragile quality in it.
Yes, the way you set the rhythm was really cool, and it's very difficult for me to fit the rhythm, so I was able to watch the recording and learn a lot about it.
That's all for the vocal recording of Wakana Matsumoto, a member of Angstrom Vivitar.
Hello Project New Member Audition 2024
Hello Project, now in its 27th year, is looking for new members!
Every member of Hello Project has experienced the same thing.
It is an audition!
The important thing is to have the courage to take the first step.
We will do our best to support your first step!
This time, we will hold auditions in two categories
If you love singing, dancing, and Hello Project!
If you love Hello Project, you can audition in the Hello Project category.
And if you want to show off your skills and personality in addition to singing and dancing, you can audition in the "Hello Project" category.
BEYOND THE POTENTIAL category!
If you want to make your dream come true with us at Hello! Project and make your dreams come true.
We are looking forward to hearing from you!
Good luck tomorrow!
Sakura Ishiyama and
and Akari Endo, it's time to say goodbye.
It's time to say goodbye!
We've seen a lot of different videos this time.
I, Endo...
Dambara from "Naimono-Love".
Dambara of Naimono-Love's vocal recording
I think it's the song we do the most
Since it's a song we often play
I was given the part of B melody.
I'm looking forward to it.
I've been getting a lot of calls from fans, but
but I'm still not there yet.
I'm going to watch Dambara's recording and learn a lot from it.
I'm going to learn a lot from your recording.
I, Ishiyama, am a fan of Morning Musume・24's music videos.
I was really impressed by the music video of Morning Musume 24's song when it was somewhat sentimental
I was really impressed by the music video of Morning Musume 24's song when it was somewhat sentimental.
It was not the image I had imagined.
I was very much impressed by the music video of Morning Musume。 The members of Morning Musume。
I'd like to see the making of this music video again and see how it was made.
I would like to see the making of this music video again.
I would like to see the music video again after watching the making of this music video.
We are going to take a look behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We're going to take you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
Please subscribe to our channel and we'll introduce you to the parts you don't usually get to see.
This time on Apkami, we'll be talking with Sakura Ishiyama of JuiceJuice and
Akari Endo of JuiceJuice
Good bye.
Next time on Apkami
Tsubaki Factory Seishun Exabyte Making of Music Video Shooting
and
the recording of BEYOND'S HIGH 2 DIAMOND!
Please look forward to it!
Next notice